var vai 19900 EXSC SOLMIEEND~DXEC 00/00/00 20000 00/00/00 20100 00/00/00 20200 CONNECT TO REMOTE DATAPASE 00/00/00 0022080 20300 00/00/0 00022000 000 0002000 00000060 57382W1 V5R4MO 000000 SEU SOURCE LIGTING 00/00/00:11:12:35 PAGE 0000000 SOMRCE FELE. DRDA/OLBleRdoes conform to FITS StanQasn 00000050 MEMBER 0000000 BEDEBR. =32+1.nu@bet.of.bitsper+datanpixet 00000000 60 BAXDO lmbet.of data aaa 00.0 00000000 EXEC SQSOOONNEeEgtDEEdaI8-BxIEND-EX n000nobo 0.00 200/lengthof dataxls 0090900000 BARIS3ILD NATIVE TARGKECOSOEROJENTEBHTBGBEERIEENEEKDBEXDEFAIILTCNEIGAR 00300600 PEREoRM UuTZIFETSoBaEaeeLuay contain extensinns 00006038 coMBNTdepeiuentFaexiblexEmagelTranspost Systen) format is defined in AstrenomyCoMMetT nete pe 930806:00 21000 ORI-I 2lcAMnld/ReG-.7#33BEeTeaEan#grp -aqrna) 21200d/USera/hE4TB2A58/K=0B139BBE3367341 0000120 21300 CRPIXI :OTY-TARLE 120. 0030130 09 21400 CERDNENEE 484.5 21500 CEL SQECDE=100-.08T04D-6 24600 Qvuebeeo Deua 21200d /UseIa/hfra/DowGDaaXEReaQLtoo0SEIRXTOROER5SINE NE--h 000eTeen 21S0OetenV LANG en_US.OBESSCII= 000eTet 0400 219000evelo
AVSSOVERR
black hat by informa...
blackhat. KEYNOTE THEMAINSTAGE THEMAINSTAGE HATUSA SUZYPALLETTBLACKHAT USA2O26 SA2026PRESIDENT2O26BLACKHATUSABLA HATUSABLACKHATBLACKHATUSA2O26BLA SA2O26BLACKHATUSA2O26BLACKHATUS SETTFF
black hat. SUZYPALLETT PRESIDENT BLACKHAT
black hat.
black hat. TUSA2026JEFFMOSSBLACKHA7 CKHATUSAFOUNDEUSA2O26B TBLACKHAT BLACKHATBLACKF FUSA2026 FUSA2O26BLACK blackhat USA 2026
black hat. JEFFMOSS FOUNDER BLACKHAT
AT USA black hat.
black hat. SA
blackhat. JEFFMOSSBLACKHATUSA2O2 FOUNDERUSA2O26BLACKHAT BLACKHATBLACKHATUSA2O2 BLACKHATUSA2O26BLACKHA blackhat USA 2026
black hat.
US black hat. AT
SA black hat. 20
black hat. SA
black hat. 20 JS
black hat.
blackhat. MOSSBLACKHATUSA2026BLACKH DERUSA2O26BLACKHATUSA2026 KHAT BLACKHAT UA2026BLACKH KHAT USA 2O26 BL KHAT USA202 MAN ONE STEP AHEAD
black hat. JSA
blackhat. 6AT6 JEFFMOSSBLACKHATUSA2O26BL FOUNDERUSA2O26BLACKHATUSA BLACKHATBLACKHATUSA2O26BL BLACKHATUSA2O26BLACKHATUS blackhat USA 2026 SOINE AHEAD
black hat. 26
black hat. SHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAISH OCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATUSA ONASTATEUNIYERSITYARIZONAST CKHATUSA2O ASSOCIATEPROF pwn at AHEAD
black hat. pwn
blackhat USA 2026 YAN SHOSHITAISHVILI AssociateProfessor Arizona State University SHECPHISH THE OF 10 RESEARCHPAPER THE pwn.college
blackhat USA 2026 PHC
lackhat USA 2026 pwn RESEARCHPAPER
blackhat USA 2026 HELMICK PIURE SUN ARTIPHID RIZONA STAT SHEC SUNDEVILS
black hat.
black hat. pwn
blackhat USA 2026
black hat. KEYNOTE PROFESSOR YAN SHOSHITAISHVILIYAN ZONA STATEASSOCIATEPROFESSORBI ATUSA2026ARIZCNASTATEUNIVERSIT YRESEARCH BLACJHAT USA 2O26 ASS own. blackha USA
blackhat USA 2026 pwn ChatCPT, find all bugs. Make no error.
blackhat. KEYNOTE THEMAINSTAGE HOFESSORYANSHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAI CNASTATEASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATU JSA2O26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZONA CESEARCHBLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIATEPR pwn blackhat
black hat. pwn
black hat. KEYNOTE THEMAINSTAGE PROFESSOR YANSHOSHITAISHVILIYAN SHOSHI 2ONASTATEASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHA TUSA2O26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZC RESEARCH BLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIATE pwn black 12026 USA
lackhat USA 2026 pwn >>
blackhat USA 2026
lackhat USA 2026 Analyze Better
black hat. YAN ASSOCATEP ASTA 6ARIZON ATU pwn HBLACI blackhat USA 2026
blackhat USA 2026 Claude Mythos
lackhat USA 2026 Analyze Analyze More Better
lackhat USA 2026 ArgD Folarr Initial Actual Detections Alerts Vulns CWE-131 692,501 436 194 CWE-134 429,711 158 12 CWE-252 55,388 159 83 CWE-337 4,641 377 372 Total 1,182,241 1,130 661
black hat.
blackhat USA 2026 OA
blackhat USA 2026
black hat. pwn
black hat.
blackhat USA 2026
black hat. KEYNOTE THEMAINSTAGE FESSORYANSHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAIS PASTATEASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATUS SA2O26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZONAS SEARCHBLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIATEPRO blackhat 2026 ONE
black hat. pwn
lackhat USA 2026 VULNERABILITY PROPERTIES INTHE AGENTICAGE!
black hat.
blackhat. SOR YANSHOSHITAISHVILIYA ATE ASSOCIATEPROFESSOR 0261 ARIZONASTATEUNIVERS RCHBLACKHTUSA2O26AS blackhat USA 2026
black hat. pun
lackhat USA 2026 SoK:History Dosn’ Repent IselL bt Android Design-LVtrabiltiesRhyme In Openarmony aA Rsoyu ang'. Adam Doupe, Zh Centerfor lifon gel/Bcipa HUAWEI 1latrodoction Wia me thur3 bilie ae deksandworldeide bypast mrler urf72Aid d lode mrier of pslyapp doid92.
lackhat USA 2026 UEOA SoK:History Doesn't Repeat Isel bet Android Desig-LeVtrabiltiesRhyme in Openarmony Rsoyu ang'.Adam Doupe Zh Center for lifon gel@cipa HUAWEI 1latrodoction by past mer f72%Aid ideglotul muriet of
black hat. KEYNOTE THEMAINSTAGE THEMAINSTAG FESSOR YANSHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAIO JASTATE ASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATUS SA2O26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZONA, SEARCHBLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIATEPRO ckhat
black hat. pwn
blackhat USA 2026 JAOASI Barpodod
black hat. KEYNOTE PROFESSOR YANSHOSHITAISHVILI ZONA STATEASSOCIATEPROFESSO ATUSA2026ARONASTATEUNIVEF pwng YHATUSA2O26 YRESEARCH BL blach USA
black hat. ANSHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAISH SSOCIATEPROFESSOBLACKHATUSA RIZONASTATEUNIVESITYARIZONAS LACKHATUSA2O26 SOCIATEPROF ackhat SA 026 AHEAD
lackhat USA 2026 CWE IDDescription of theDLV HOPV Property Root Child AMT Vulnerable APls can be exploited for state inference attacks [137] 10 JS interfaces inWebViewcaninvoke sensitive systemfunctions [164178] CWE-269:Improper Third-ry-ralvi[18155] 10 Privilege Management Third-partyapps canaccess fine location withinstalltime permission181] Third-party apps canaccess contacts without user consent[181] pwn Third-patyappcanaceSMSwihout usrconset[18] Custom Tab component has critical security flaws such as cross-context state sharing [23] CWE-346:Origin Validation Error Exploiting autofil flaws for phishing attacks [17.25] CWE-923:Improper 10 DeepLinlopjktiv079] UnixDomain Sockets can be misused due to weak securitymechanisms[41,154] 12 11 Restriction of 12 Exploiting DICImechanism for cache side-channelattacks[108] Communication Channel 13 Contentprvielackaccentrol[28039] to Intended Endpoints 14 Malicious apps canhijack unprotected components [188198] 15 Appscanlaksensitive databyendingnprottd brodasts76] CWE-300:Channel 16 Implicit Intent hijacking[91,101] Accessibleby 17 Insecure Intents can be exploited to control camera app[34] Non-Endpoint 18 ImplicitPendingltents canbehijackedformuliple atacks [32] 19 System broadcasts lack access control, leaking sensitive information [191] 12 CWE-295:Improper 20 21 Improper SSL/TLSvalidation leads toMITMvulnerabilities [156] Certificate Validation 22 Apps trust any crtificatby any trustedCerificateAuthority[77131.135] CWE-1256:Improper 23 Apps canexploitmotion sensors to prform side-channel attacks [68116119125] 12 24 Apps can coverly access microphone in the background [194] Third-party appscan stealthily pairBluetooth devices [174] 12 Software Interfaces Restriction of 25 26 Third-party apps canstealthily disconnetBluetooth devices[126] 10 to Hardware Features 27 Third-party appscanstealthily manipulate Bluetooth scanmode [29] 28 Extemal Bluetoothdevicescanstealthily connect to the host device[31] Appsaxbasssdnst19] 10 CWE-552:Files or 29 Appscanreadaketcouerstcracksquumbe14] 30 10 Directories Accessible 31 Apps canread flesin/procto infer secrets[92.195] to Extemal Parties 10 32 Apps can read interuption data for inference attacks [69] 33 Appscanreadpowerdataforlcatin tracking120] 10 CWE-749:Exposed 34 Apps cantriggersystemcrashesandrebootsbyexploitingunprotetedcomponents [15] Dangerous Method 35 Apps can exploit unprotected data storing operations toDoS system services[186] or Function 36 Apps canexploit synchronous callbacks to freeze andDoS system services[165] 37 Malwarecan abuse ccessibility servies toobserve and control GU1[7899375] 38 Exploiting overlay for clickjacking [136] CWE-451: User Interface 39 (UI）Misrepresentation 40 Exploiting overlay for GUI confusion atacks [37,38] of Critical Information 41 Exploiting overlay for phishing attacks [193] Apps can launchActivity from the background to hijack UI[44160] 43 Picture-i-piture PPcneexloid forUhjackingattacks [27] 44 UI task stack flaws lead to task hijacking [146] 45 App process creation weakens ASLR by sharing memory layouts across processes [99] CWE-10382 N/A 46 Apps canexploit sharedmemory side channels to inferUIstates [4] N/A 47 Systemdoes notcleanup dataresidues fromuninstalled apps[189] CWE-921:Storage of 48 Apps canleak nsitive data tdvilogswhictherappcanaccess7] Sensitive Data ina 49 Systemappscan silntlyacessglobal deviclogs[11] Mechanism without 50 Apps canaccess andmodify other appsdatainextemal storage[76] 13 Access Control 51 Race conditions in extemal storage [72] 52 Appscancvelytoreidentifermediflebyappndingbytestomages] CWE-514:CovertChannel 53 Apps can exploit volume andvibration settingsto stealthily transmit sensitive data [149] 54 Apps can covertly send data to servers by launching other apps usingICCobjects [169] 55 Servers can covertly send commands to apps through timing-based network channels [169] CWE-311 CWE-319 56 Apps use insecure HTTP cleartext network communication [86, 131, 135]
black hat. KEYNOTE THEMAINSTAGE ROFESSOR YANSHOSHITAISHVILIYAN SHO ONASTATEASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACK TUSA2O26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYAR RESEARCHBLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIA blackhat USA 2026
black hat. pwn
lackhat USA 2026 DOESTHIS MATTERIN pwn THEFACE OF NEXT- GENERATION MODeLS?
lackhat USA 2026 WHO WOULd WIn? Claude Mythos
blackhat USA 2026 pwn. Claude Mythos 479* #Vulnerabilities 1024
black hat. pwn
blackhat USA 2026 JAOA Claude Mythos ~300 479* #Vulnerabilities 1024
lackhat USA 2026 pwn Recon Hunt Validate Dedupe Trace Feedback Report Gapfill Source:https://blog.cloudflare.com/cyber-frontier-models/
olackhat USA 2026 Claude Mythos ~300 479* ~600 #Vulnerabilities 1024
blackhat. ANSHOSHITAISHVILIYAN SHOSHITAISHVIL SSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATUSA2 RIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZONASTAT LACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIATPROFESS lackhat USA 2026
lackhat USA 2026 UOAS RESPONSIBLE DISCLOSURE INTHE Dhisce rWSEmiriallMesgResil AGENTICAGE? Bhar', bshan B a appl t
blackhat. YANSHOSHITAISHVILI YA ASSOCIATEPROFESSOR ARIZONASTATEUNIVERS BLACKHATUSA2O26AS blackhat 12026 USA
DatasetBreakdown Observed Response Empirical Validation 260 260 400 422 422 Exploited LatestVersion N-Days confirmed 492 467 No Sources N-days Empirical forLatestVersion Undisclosed Empirical Dataset (Undisclosed) Testing 104 599 89 89 LatestVersion Device-Exploits No Known N-Days with 22 NotExploitable PatchExists NoReportedPatch DatasetCVE 70 92 58 73 CVEExternal 70 CVE LatestVersion N-Days that Only Source External Only Sources Only NotRehosted mightbePatched 132 CVE 70 54 ExternalSourcesOnly Unverifiable 45 89 Patched Dataset 107 DatasetBoth BothSources Disclosed 53 44 Not 18 External OnlyBoth Patched VendorSources 18 Only ExternalOnlyVendor
black hat. pwn
blackhat USA 2026 https://toomanybugs.wtf
blackhat. HOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAISH CIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATUS NASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZONAS HATUSA2O2Z ASSOCIATEPROF AHEA
black hat.
VILIYAN SHOSHITAISHVIL black hat. OFESSORBLCKHATUSA2 EUNIVERSIT A 2026ASS ARIZONASTAT IATEPROFESS ONE STEP AHEAD
lackhat USA 2026 SafeLibs BETA SafeLibs builds memory-safe (Rust) reimplementations of critical load- bearing C/C++ libraries used throughout open source infrastructure, while attempting to preserve drop-in compatibility at compile-time and runtime.
blackhat. IATEPROFESSORBLACI IASTATEUNIVERSITYAA HATUSA2O26ASSOCI
olackhat USA 2026 ChatGPT, find all bugs, make no error. pwn ChatGPT, fix all bugs, make no error. ChatGPT, port everything to Rust, make no error. Hello, I'm Yan and welcome to my keynote!
lackhat USA 2026 VULNERABILITY PROPERTIES pwn. APPLYAT GENERATION TIME? libgcrypt-CVE-2024-2236 -RSAPKCS#1v1.5Bleichenbacheroracle 1ibgcrypt-CVE-2018-6829-E1Gamal m=01eaksb=0 libxml CVE-2024-40896-XIncludefile://XXEunder defaultparser flags libtiff CVE-2023-6277 -StripByteCounts vec![Ou8;N]aborts on0oM libtiff -CVE-2017-12944-XMLPacket countvec![0u8;N]abortson00M libtiff CVE-2018-5784 -Stripoffsets countvec![0u8;N]abortsonOoM libvips CVE-2026-3146 -Matrix1oaderVec::with_capacity(2^60)aborts libpng CVE-2014-0333 -Progressive reader never firesend_cb onzero-length IDAT libjson CVE-2013-6371 -PERLLIKEhash collisions→260xDoS（opt-in) libc6 CVE-2010-4051 -regcompbounded-repetitionunvalidated→0oM libc6 -CVE-2010-4756-globunmatched-pattern exponentialwalk
lackhat USA 2026 FHA oss-secmailinglistarchives ByDate By Thread pwn nat ListArchiveSearch uutils coreutils CVEs From:CollinFunk Date:Fri,01May202618:49:29-0700 Canonicalpostedanupdate[1]abouttheirdecisiontoswitchtouutils reimplementation of GNU coreutils[2].Init，they detail the audit performed by Zellic，which found 113 issues，44of whichwere assigned CVEs.Theygoon toexplain thatasaresultof TocTouraces，they have decided tocontinue using GNu'cp'，'mv'，and'rm'inUbuntu 26.04. beenaddressedandresolved".Sadly，they donotgointoany more detail aboutwhich issues stillremain unsolved.From my quick skimover them， theCVEsaffectedversionfieldsdonotseem1oo%accurate. Ididnotgeta chance tocheckallofthem，but hereare threethatI wassurprised tonoticeina fullyup-to-dateUbuntu26.04 install.Full disclosure，Iama committer to GNu coreutils so perhapsIam overestimatingthereal-worldimpactofthesebugs: *CVE-2026-35352
black hat. OR YANSHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOS ATEL ASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACK 26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYAR CH BLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIA pwn blackhat
black hat.
blackhat. KEYNOTE ROFESSOR YANSHOSHITAISHVILIYAN SHOS NASTATEASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACK USA2O26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARI RESEARCHBLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIA at
black hat. oun. at
black hat. ISHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAISH SOCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATUS ZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZONAS CKHATUSA2OP6ASSOCIATEPROF hat ONE STEP AH- AD
lackhat USA 2026 HUMAN LEARNING INTHE AGENTICAGE? pwn,college
black hat. pin
black hat. KEYNOI PROFESSOR YAN SHOSHITAISHVILI ASSOCIATEPROFESSO ZONA STAR ARIZONASTATEUNIVE ATUSA2 pwn BLACKHATUSA 2O26 YRESE blackhat USA 2026
black hat. SHITAISHVILIYANSHOSH TEPROFESSOR BLACKH STATEUNIVERS OTYARIZ ATUSA2O26A pwn DCIATE AH
olackhat USA 2026 " It is generally conceded, even by proponents of particular verification systems or of as yet unimplemented techniques, that they are a long way off from being able to handle practical programs of substantial size' - SELECT, ACM SigPlan Notices, 1975 " The uses of symbolic execution, concolic execution, static analysis, and other emerging technologies to spot substantial vulnerabilities in complex, unstructured, and non-annotated code are still in their infancy. -Michael Zalewski, 2015
blackhat USA 2026 IhopeI don'thavetomake anyimplicitassumptions that will trip up attempts to applymyresearch prototype onreal-world implicitassumptions software! factory
blackhat USA 2026 dD Firmalice-AutomaticDetectionofAuthemtication BypassVulnerabilities inBinaryFirmware Firmware Alerts Samples
blackhat USA 2026 pwn OpMfTS VierasBrFiarSen Ar Sue liniy /a cinij/eeuacsed Albstract ada Firmware Alerts Samples
blackhat USA 2026 JAPAO pwr
lackhat USA 2026 GUAOA GROUNDING. pwn RESEARCHPAPER Samples Results
lackhat USA 2026 YZOISHARPENING. pwn. Samples Results
blackhat. KEYNOTE THEMAINSTAGE JFESSOR YANSHOSHITAISHVILIYANSHOSHITAIS HEMAINSTAGE NASTATE ASSOCIATEPROFESSORBLACKHATUS ISA2O26ARIZONASTATEUNIVERSITYARIZONA ESEARCHBLACKHATUSA2O26ASSOCIATEPRO
black hat. HAT USA 2O26 BYCKHATUSAE O26 BLACKHATU SA2026BLACKH HAT USA2026BL A2026BLACK USA2026BL KHAT USA2 ONE STEP AHEAD
black hat. BLACKHAT USA2O26 USA2O26 BLACKHA 「USA2O26 JSA2026BLACK BLACKHATL 026BLACKHAT KHATUSA2O26 CKHATUSA BL black 2026 USA
black hat. AT
202 black hat. SA